Damn it, Mob.
You could've let me know
if you had other plans.
Why do you think I gave you a cellphone?
You can drop me off here.
Th-Thank you. That'll be 8,810 yen.
"Hakata Salt"
S-Sir? What are you going
to do out here so late?
Don't worry. I'm not
planning to do anything rash.
What the heck is he doing out here?
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 9%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
I-It's okay, Ritsu.
I'm pretty sure it's this way.
Okay...
This is the same place as earlier.
I'm sorry, Ritsu. It's my fault for
saying we should go exploring...
Forget the apologies.
Let's focus on finding a way back.
Yeah... But how?
Oh, I know!
--Ritsu?
--I learned this in science class.
The side with moss growing on it is north.
Moss always grows where
the sun doesn't shine much!
See?
This way is north. If we walk
this way, we'll get to the river.
Then we can get back to
where we were barbecuing.
Let's go, Nii-san.
Yeah!
Looks like you're awake.
Where am I--
Are you all right?
Do you remember how you lost?
Not at all...
Nii-san, does your head hurt?
What could it be? Nothing serious, I hope.
I hope you didn't suffer any brain damage.
Ritsu...
I'm so glad you're okay.
You're okay, right?
--Nii-san...
--Let's hurry home. Right, Hanazawa-kun?
We can't. I'm not sure why,
but we can't use our powers in this room.
It was futile, no matter
how many times I tried.
Usually, it'd be easy for me
to bust a hole into this wall.
Oh, you're right.
But that's okay. Ritsu's with us.
Huh?
What can your little brother do?
He's really smart.
Unlike me, who can't do anything
without psychic powers,
he can figure anything out
and solve any problem.
Even without relying on powers.
You're proud of him, huh?
So much so that you rely on him.
I admire him. I admire him immensely.
That's not fair...
You won't even let me apologize.
That's not fair!
Even I...
I---
Your sealed room is amazing
as usual, Sakurai-kun.
Of course. That aside, what now?
Are we going to make those intruders
a new part of the upper echelon?
You're jumping the gun.
First, we need to brainwash them thoroughly.
Hey, hold on a second, you guys.
Are you planning to turn
decent talent into junk?
That group of middle schoolers
will be recruited to HQ.
Suzuki-kun, was it?
I call all the shots in the 7th Division,
including personnel decisions.
I'm going to take them,
especially the kid in the uniform.
We really connected.
He'll be a great friend.
Quit acting like you're more
than a temp trainee.
I'm not very kind.
Oh, don't get so mad.
Are you actually upset about
your coworkers being defeated?
Apparently, you guys got along
better than I thought.
Calm down, old man.
--That was a compliment.
--Stop it, Sakurai.
Everyone at HQ hates one another.
I feel at home here.
Hmph. Kids these days...
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
--Is he with the intruders?
--What do you want?
Hey, get the others!
Hey, what are you guys talking about?
What's going on inside?
Don't move, you suspicious jerk!
Tell us who you are!
Oh, yeah...
Does he have a gun?! Be careful.
Ah... Crap.
I ran out of business cards.
--B-Business cards?
--Did he say business cards?
Anyway, listen, you guys.
Is something going on inside?
--S-Stay back!
--We have nothing to say to some weird outsider!
Hmm... That's strange.
I'm usually informed
when something happens,
but I haven't heard anything.
--What are you talking about?
--Could he mean...
So, let me get straight to the point.
Can you all use psychic powers?
--H-How does he know about that?
--He knows about our organization?
He's acting pretty important...
Sorry, but I'm getting nowhere with you guys.
Hold it, you damned intruder!
S-Stop it! He might be...
I think so, too...
Let go.
I'm only here to talk about work
with my subordinate.
Subordinate?
Subordinate? Could it be...?
Everyone here is the
7th Division Leader's subordinate.
But Division Leader Ishiguro is
a direct subordinate of the boss...
Which means...
I was so rude!
I-I'm going to be killed!
What? Are you not feeling well?
Hey, someone help him in.
Surely you guys have a break room.
H-He's so kind!
He totally exudes a superior aura...
It's gotta be him!
He's Claw's boss!
--He's come back to Japan!
--He's coming through!
Make way!
Pardon me. Reporting!
--What is it?
--The boss is here from HQ.
What?
But he said he'd be coming next month.
Hm?
Someone just hid.
What?! It's either an intruder or an escapee!
--Capture them!
--Yeah!
We got caught again.
Hey, don't be violent to kids.
S-Sorry, Boss!
So you are their boss.
No, I'm not that important.
Oh, come on, now.
The real deal doesn't brag to children.
Looks like we might actually
be able to get through to him.
Um, we were suddenly kidnapped
and held captive here.
Our friend is still in custody.
Please help!
Were you guys really doing that?
Huh? But we were just following orders...
--You're blaming others?
--I'm very sorry!
Not to mention, it's not right
to commit villainy
just because you were ordered to.
When underlings get too obedient,
they're nothing but trash.
B-But... We believed in--
You fools!
Even if you're able to
rise to the top like that,
all you'll see when you look down
is the filth you left in your wake.
I'm not sure what you're trying to do,
but getting to the top only feels good
when you do it the right way!
Repent and reflect!
T-True...
We've been doing such petty things...
W-Wow, they changed instantly...
I guess the boss would be
in a league of his own.
Have you thought of anything, Ritsu?
It's probably best we don't
try anything right now.
They'll come check on us for sure.
Let's conserve our energy until then.
You're right. The moment we get our
powers back will be the decisive moment.
We can count on your strength,
too, right, Little Brother?
--Huh?
--It's my fault for involving you two.
I'll do what I can.
Will he be okay?
Hey, I was almost burned to death.
But, well, if you get serious,
the two of us won't even have to fight.
They're here.
And they're moving in a pack, as always.
Hey, Mob. What the heck
are you doing in a place like this?
Oh, your little brother's
here, too. What's up?
Wh-Who are you?
Do you know the Kageyama brothers?
Hey! Don't talk that way to the boss!
--The boss?!
--What are you doing here, Master?
Master?!
Is that a wi--
Who's he? Your friend?
Th-That's Kageyama-kun's
master and Claw's boss?
But this is our chance!
We're being held here against our will!
Please let us go!
Why do you have them trapped in here?
Huh? Well...
"Whisper Whisper"
"Whisper Whisper" --Why are you whispering?
--Well, it's top secret...
"Whisper Whisper"
No, really...
Guys, that's a crime.
We're very sorry!
You're amazing, Master.
Did he really manage to fool them?
--Anyway, let's get out of here.
--Are we saved...? --Okay.
Boss, where are you going?
I said we're leaving.
You should at least wait for
Division Leader Ishiguro...
"Mob Psycho 100"
Who are you?
You're not the boss.
Introduce yourselves,
you criminal organization.
I'm Ishiguro, the 7th Division Leader
of the psychic association, Claw.
Who might you be?
The greatest psychic in modern history,
Reigen Arataka-sama.
Look me up.
--What?!
--He's not our boss?
Fraud or not,
you had the nerve to disregard me
and call yourself the boss...
That's a severe offense.
What are you talking about, you shrimp?
I'll take care of you with my green belt
in Shorinji Kenpo with a snap--
--Strong!
--Huh? What is this?
Master, you're a spirit specialist.
Stand back.
I see. You've gathered some efficient pawns.
If you gather enough, you might
actually be able to oppose Claw.
--D-Division Leader!
--At that angle, we'll die, too!
Like I care. That guy's your boss, isn't he?
N-No...
--All of you, hide in some rooms!
--Huh?
If you wanna make it big,
you can't die here!
This is your chance to be freed from
the shackles of this black organization.
Hurry up. Leave this to my student and go!
You're such a...
--Thank you!
--Run away!
Actually, I'll be going, too...
The ceiling!
You're not getting away.
Whoa, what is going on?
There are seriously espers other than Mob?
I'm no match for that power...
Actually, they're pretty
difficult for me, too.
Which means...
Kageyama-kun!
It's up to you.
Yes. He's strong.
I'll take care of him.
I'm pretty sure he's never met
anyone stronger than him yet.
Sadly, you won't get anywhere close to me...
And you'll be squished.
--Nii-san!
--Gravity control?!
Mob, what are you doing?
Master...
You're not bad, being able
to resist my powers.
Why don't we increase the gravity a bit?
Anti-Esper Dropkick!
"Anti-Esper Dropkick"
This is one of Reigen's special moves,
"Anti-Esper Dropkick" where he
dropkicks an esper as hard as he can.
Where he dropkicks an esper
as hard as he can.
--Master...
--Mob.
Are you planning on fighting these guys
with your psychic powers?
Didn't I tell you that it's dangerous
to use them against others?
Are you going to break the rule?
He had a rule like that?
In order to save me, he had no choice!
Mob...
You felt that cornered?
It must have been rough.
Confronting others is
the hardest thing for him,
especially confronting adults like you.
Watching you guys bully a kid who's
so awkward and gets easily discouraged
definitely doesn't make me feel good.
Stop stressing out my student!
Then, are you going to fight instead?
Guys, let me tell you something...
You're not supposed to harm others.
But dropkicks are okay?
But if you're not going to listen,
I'll fight you.
Due to my position as
their temporary guardian,
I'm not going to let them fight.
I'll fight you, as peacefully as possible.
First, let's see what you've got.
I'll show you my hypnosis!
"Five Yen"
Look at this five yen coin.
--How foolish.
--Something's wrong.
I don't sense anything from him.
Kageyama-kun's master's powers...
So he actually is an esper?
If this is a ruse,
it's going to be dangerous.
While you're watching this...
...Hypnosis Punch!
"Hypnosis Punch"”
"Hypnosis Punch"” This is one of Reigen's special
moves, where he suddenly punches his opponent.
This is one of Reigen's special moves,
where he suddenly punches his opponent.
He just hit him!
Those weren't special powers at all.
You guys...
Quit messing around!
What's up with that?
That's a really sharp katana!
Jugan. This is actually
a toy sword made out of plastic,
"Jugan" Jugan. This is actually
But after wearing it and
cursing it over the years,
but after wearing it and
it actually became powerful.
Uh, hold on. Listen...
Come out, my little ones.
Do you think you can handle my little
evil spirits that I've nurtured?
--No really, listen.
--Ethereal Bodies Technique.
"Ethereal Bodies Technique"
I can freely exit my physical body,
and I can even clone my ethereal form.
"Ethereal Bodies Technique"
Come on, you're dealing with children.
Maybe I'll get a little angry.
Black Orbs. Let the varying gravity
from them rip you apart.
"Black Orbs" Black Orbs. Let the
varying gravity from them rip you apart.
Black Orbs. Let the varying gravity
from them rip you apart.
Reigen's plan backfired.
I was going to try to reason with them
while they were panicked from being hit,
but I just pissed them off!
I messed up!
Reigen was very confident in
defeating others in arguments.
He had never lost to anyone in an argument,
no matter who they were.
But that's only when I'm
actually dealing with adults.
These brutes who are actually seriously
attacking middle school kids...
These guys who are seriously talking
about taking over the world...
...are children who failed to grow up.
How did they end up like this?
The answer is simple...
--Mob, we're getting outta here!
--Die!
I'm being pulled in!
Crap! Pull him back!
Master!
Ow!
While I don't like the idea of
being sucked into a black hole,
don't rip my body apart by pulling too hard!
Maybe I went too far.
Come on, now...
You can blow them away
with psychic powers?
--Give it a try.
--Wha--?
Little Brother!
I'm surprised you were able to dodge that.
But... you look better that way.
Dang it... There are some weirdos back there.
If they were evil spirits,
I'd be able to exorcise them...
Exorcise?
Just try it.
Huh?
I guess you can just exorcise them.
Come out, my ultimate creation...
...Candy-chan!
You can wreak as much havoc
as you'd like today!
We're getting out of here.
Don't bother with them, Mob!
Kageyama-kun, use all of your powers!
Just blow these guys away!
Stop! Don't fight back!
I'm an adult, so I'll deal with them!
Mob, there's no need for you
to stoop to their level!
Nii-san's the only one that
stands a chance anymore!
Ritsu... You're right.
I have to defeat them...
No! Don't! Don't fight back, Mob!
Ritsu's hurt...
We have to fight power with power!
At this rate, we're all going to die!
We just need to run away!
There's no way for us to run while
dealing with their fierce attacks!
Come on! Use the powers
you used back then!
Calm down! Don't go head-on with
someone who has murderous intent, Mob!
All four of you are going to hell.
Ritsu... Hanazawa-kun... Master Reigen...
I can't let them all die.
I have no choice but to
fight with all I've got.
If I can protect them, I don't care
what happens to my opponents!
"Murderous Intent"
Don't do it, Mob. You're the one
who's going to suffer in the end.
When things go south,
it's okay to run away!
"Master"
"~Leader~"
"Spirits and Such Consulting Office"
Excuse me. I came here
because I saw your sign.
Sure thing.
How may I help you?
Er... Oh, it's just a kid.
What do you want, boy?
Um, I'm an esper.
--Wha--?
--There are times when I can't control my powers very well,
and it's scary.
Did someone tell you to
come here and tell me that?
No. I haven't been able to
talk to anyone about this.
I thought you might be the same as me...
If I tried, I could see spirits, too.
Well, come on in.
Okay.
I was troubled a lot when I was a kid, too.
Listen. Just because you have psychic powers
doesn't make you any less human.
It's the same as people who are fast,
people who are book smart,
and people with strong body odor.
Psychic powers are just
another characteristic.
You must embrace that as a part of yourself
and continue to live positively.
The truth behind one's charm is kindness.
Become a good person. That is all.
May I come to talk to you again?
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I'm pretty busy, you know?
Anyway, you should go home for tod-- Hot!
Hey, don't get bur--
Hey... You said you could
see ghosts, too, right?
Do you know how to exorcise them, too?
All right. Come again tomorrow
around the same time.
What? Really?
I'll show you how to use your powers.
Master!
Master...
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
After being hurt on a whim
something from somewhere
is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
"Yes n "No n
Huh? Master...?
Master! Master!
Please wake up, Master!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 12:
"Mob and Reigen."
This was in Master's will:
"Mob and Reigen"
"Mob and Reigen" Watching the finale
in real time is an excellent decision.